I have to treat them nice, do it with a smile, do everything I can just to keep the situation calm.
Do what I got to do.
Customers are customers.
Sometimes you get nice ones and sometimes you get not so nice ones.
I'm going to go ahead and check and see how they're doing, fill some drinks, and hopefully it goes well.
So guys, how is everything going here?
Can you take any longer with our drinks?
Actually, the bartender is working on that.
They're working as fast as they can.
I promise you'll they'll be out.
The bartender.
There's always excuses, always excuses.
Yeah, I'm really sorry, like I said, I put your order in.
It's on its way.
They're working as fast as they can.
And our food?
Actually, I put the order in.
It should be out in probably 5 minutes.
5 minutes?
Make it 3.
Okay, well I'll go ahead, check on it, and see if they can get it out any faster.
I'll be back.
I'll let you know how it's going.
Yeah, you do that.
Alright.